this tutorial is about curved shapes
本教程是关于弯曲形状的
那就是围绕着折痕
this tutorial is about curved shapes
that is the taking the crease around the
弯曲，这是最简单的
给你喙或鼻子，这是一个
that is the taking the crease around the
bend so this is at its most simple it
这样更极端的例子
如果您正在折痕全部
bend so this is at its most simple it
gives you a beak or a nose this is a
围绕完整曲线的方式
不再是另一个例子了
gives you a beak or a nose this is a
more more extreme example so in this
一直围绕着曲线
这两个之间的区别
more more extreme example so in this
case you're taking the the crease all
一个基于平行折叠这一
基于差异
case you're taking the the crease all
the way around a complete curve and here
两者之间的解释如下
教程1的介绍，所以我就
the way around a complete curve and here
isn't another example again it's taking
给你看几个例子
显然在行动中这是一个非常
isn't another example again it's taking
it all the way around the curve
简单简单一个又一次
绕着一条曲线，
it all the way around the curve
the difference between these two this
其他这是一个观点折叠
这是在教程3这个例子中
the difference between these two this
one is based on parallel folds this one
是平行折叠的弯曲形状
你的鱼一路走来
one is based on parallel folds this one
is based on refold the difference
你可以看到这里我们有一小块
添加使这些弯曲的尾巴
is based on refold the difference
between these two is explained in
您可以在任何点上贴块的形状
在曲线上，他们会在
between these two is explained in
tutorial 1 the introduction so I'll just
不同的角度，所以很有趣
玩这里还有另一个例子
tutorial 1 the introduction so I'll just
show you a couple of examples
在这种情况下，这是基于v折
在这种情况下，耳朵是
show you a couple of examples
obviously in action this is a very
选项卡，将作品粘贴到页面上，然后
整个东西很坚固
obviously in action this is a very
simple simple one it's just again it's
结构，以便您可以切块
像
simple simple one it's just again it's
just going around one curve and the
狗的数学已经被删掉了，所以
我将首先向您展示如何
just going around one curve and the
other this is a point of view fold
使小弯曲的形状成为喙或
鼻子放在这个内置的沟渠中
other this is a point of view fold
that's in tutorial 3 this example this
这是我们制造的水上飞机
教程12取一小张卡片
that's in tutorial 3 this example this
is the parallel fold curved shape giving
将其折成一半的纵向折痕
非常好，将其制成V型折叠
is the parallel fold curved shape giving
you the fish it comes all the way around
正如我们在教程2中所做的那样，
这样的折痕是第一次
you the fish it comes all the way around
you can see here we've got a small piece
在这边增加你在做什么
这是一对折叠，给您一个
you can see here we've got a small piece
added to make the tail with these curved
有点向下箭头，只是
切成几个粘合片
added to make the tail with these curved
shapes you can stick pieces on any point
所以这是现在做另一个
折叠它可以是任何角度
shapes you can stick pieces on any point
on the curve and they'll stick out at a
根据您想要的形状
创建，使像这样的折叠
on the curve and they'll stick out at a
different angle so it's quite fun to
靠自己打开它，所以现在
你又有一个向下指点
different angle so it's quite fun to
play with there's another example here
箭头切出它的一侧，所以你
减少更长的折痕，所以在这里
play with there's another example here
in this case this is based on the v-fold
有一个与此匹配的小屋
折边的另一面，你使
in this case this is based on the v-fold
and in this case the ears these are the
放到粘贴标签中，然后向下折叠，
弄好它，所以现在就开始
and in this case the ears these are the
tabs that glue the piece to the page and
像这样把你的胶折叠起来
把它放在选项卡上，在这里我们
tabs that glue the piece to the page and
the whole thing is quite a solid rigid
是
把它折叠起来，现在整个
the whole thing is quite a solid rigid
structure so you can cut chunks away
应该放平并根据如何
你坚持下去会影响什么
structure so you can cut chunks away
like the
塑造您创建的形状，因此我们将
将其粘贴到此沟渠中
like the
the math of the dog has been cut away so
我刚要去的水上飞机
削减一些我想我有
the math of the dog has been cut away so
I'll just start by showing you how to
标签有点大，所以涂上胶水
一侧决定您想要的形状
I'll just start by showing you how to
make a small curved shape a beak or a
做吧，这会是你知道的
真的很广泛下降了很多
make a small curved shape a beak or a
nose onto this built into this gully of
伸出很多
确保中央折痕
nose onto this built into this gully of
this this floating plane that we made in
胶水，请确保中央折痕
这个鼻梁排成一排
this this floating plane that we made in
tutorial 12 take a small piece of card
在水面上的沟壑，你
将胶水放在另一个卡口上，关闭底座
tutorial 12 take a small piece of card
fold it in half lengthways crease it
用力按在那里
曲线上最简单的变化
fold it in half lengthways crease it
really well and make this into a V fold
形状向您展示如何制作其中一种
以鱼为基础
really well and make this into a V fold
as we did in tutorial 2 so you make a
片
彻底喝下沉淀屏
as we did in tutorial 2 so you make a
crease like this this is the first
另一张黄牌
只是通过学习将眼睛切成两半
crease like this this is the first
crease up this side what you're making
将其折成两半
并在其上再展开两个折痕
crease up this side what you're making
here is a pair of folds that give you a
这些是粘合片的外边缘
厘米或半英寸宽
here is a pair of folds that give you a
sort of downward pointing arrow and just
得到了这三个折痕或
现在您实际上只想要
sort of downward pointing arrow and just
cut that to make a couple of gluing tabs
中间的胶合片大约一英寸
到两厘米半
so here's the piece now make another
厘米之类的东西，所以你
可以切掉你大部分的东西
so here's the piece now make another
fold it can be any angle really
折叠，所以你有这样的一块
打开，您在每一侧都有一个标签
fold it can be any angle really
depending on what shape you want to
您现在可以逐一加固
现在拿一支铅笔开始
depending on what shape you want to
create so make something like this fold
顶部有一个标记，这是顶部折痕
因此，使两个标记与
create so make something like this fold
that back on itself open it up so now
标签的角落很深，所以
你有两个这样的标记
that back on itself open it up so now
you've got another downward pointing
大约还有三分之一的分数
外边缘，所以这将是
you've got another downward pointing
arrow cut out one side of it so you're
您的曲线，以便您可以在上面绘制曲线
像这样，然后你
arrow cut out one side of it so you're
cutting a longer crease so here you've
你把这条曲线分解成一系列
短的直边，所以我就去
cutting a longer crease so here you've
got a cottage that is matching this this
两个，这样你就做一个标记，
现在，这些将是直的
got a cottage that is matching this this
folded edge the other side you make that
边缘在这里，所以您只需要切割
这很关键，您只需切下
folded edge the other side you make that
into a gluing tab and fold that down and
一侧，所以在这里切出并切成这些
直线
into a gluing tab and fold that down and
crease it well so this is now just going
这边也一样，所以你
有一块这样的东西现在折成
crease it well so this is now just going
to fold shut like that put your glue
它的关闭位置并标记那些
那些杯状线是撒谎的，所以在这里他们是如此
put it on the put it on the tab here we
当您现在打开它时，您可以看到
您的行与
put it on the put it on the tab here we
are
剪线，所以这些将成为制表符
建立在那些被切掉的东西上
fold it shut and now the whole piece
现在您可以将冰块折叠成标签
沿这些线折叠将其折回
fold it shut and now the whole piece
should just go flat and according to how
他们自己
我们去确保折痕是
should just go flat and according to how
you stick it down that will affect what
很好，在这种情况下，您
将胶水同时放在所有四个标签上
you stick it down that will affect what
shape you create and so we're going to
时间，然后您可以将其折叠
然后将整张纸对折
shape you create and so we're going to
stick it here into this gully created on
所以只要确保全部
工作正常，现在可以很好地打开了
stick it here into this gully created on
the the floating plane I'm just going to
这将沿着你的脊椎
这样的东西，但你会看到
the the floating plane I'm just going to
cut these back a bit I think I've got
因为这些角落仍然存在
袋进入页面，因此您将
cut these back a bit I think I've got
the tabs a little bit big so put glue on
必须将它们切成曲线
匹配页面，这取决于什么
the tabs a little bit big so put glue on
one side decide what shape you want to
切掉的角度取决于一切
基本形状使您走得更远
one side decide what shape you want to
make so is it going to be you know
所以我们就这样尝试吧
不，您可以看到，现在适合
make so is it going to be you know
really wide coming down a lot or
放在页面上，就可以拥有
选项卡出来，或者您可以将它们放在
really wide coming down a lot or
sticking out quite a lot
每周您打算走多远
看看你需要多远
sticking out quite a lot
make sure the central crease of this
从脊椎向下粘到一侧
在那边放胶水
make sure the central crease of this
glue so make sure the central crease of
一边关闭它
承受很大的压力，所以你
glue so make sure the central crease of
this this nose piece is lined up with
知道确保它确实是胶水
牢牢地固定好你的身材
this this nose piece is lined up with
the gully on the floating plane and you
它是
这种形状会在每个
the gully on the floating plane and you
put glue on the other tab close the base
你可以建在那边
这条山折一直延伸
put glue on the other tab close the base
press it firmly there you have it
可以在您之上建立
也可以在上面挖个洞
press it firmly there you have it
the most simple variation on the curved
一个真正抽象的小例子
件添加到它，所以我们在这里
the most simple variation on the curved
shapes show you how to make one of these
v形卡在其上的沟中
我们的每一侧都有插槽切入
shapes show you how to make one of these
that the fish was based on take a base
通过这些进入它的主体
贴在这里，我们有一个
that the fish was based on take a base
sheet
多余的东西卡在山上
将所有这些v形泡沫缝隙
sheet
drink precip screens thoroughly take
小小的碎片，它们都是
最后我会在其他教程中介绍
drink precip screens thoroughly take
another piece cards we'll go with yellow
只是给你看一些书中的例子
海伦轰炸机的丛林时代，这里是
cut it in half just by eyes learning to
弯曲形状的使用非常漂亮
大象的这头鬼屋
cut it in half just by eyes learning to
measure fold it in half crease it well
通过lampion caskey是一个非常奇怪的
小弯曲的形状从
and unfold two more creases onto the
带有螺旋的页面是
用餐Autopia
and unfold two more creases onto the
outer edge these are the gluing tabs one
James Gurney的晚餐拓扑，就在这里
说这是弯曲的形状
outer edge these are the gluing tabs one
centimeter or half an inch wide you've
恐龙的顶端是彩色的
在这种情况下，它被构建在盒子上
centimeter or half an inch wide you've
got these three three creases or
机制和盒子机制是什么
我们将在下一个教程中进行
got these three three creases or
parallel now you only actually want
教程14最后，这很棒
尼克·巴特沃思（Nick Butterworth）和米克（Mick）
parallel now you only actually want
gluing tabs in the middle about one inch
墨水笔，其中只有一个弹出窗口
但这确实是一个了不起的用途
gluing tabs in the middle about one inch
to centimeters two and a half
弯曲的形状，您已经拥有了它
在你的结构外面
to centimeters two and a half
centimeters something like that so you
也把它放在
方面以及我们研究过的所有内容
centimeters something like that so you
can cut cut away the bulk of what you
我的书涵盖了本教程
弹出式设计和纸张力学
can cut cut away the bulk of what you
folded so you have a piece like this
您